

OWUSU WILLIAM Frontend Developer

ABOUT ME

I'm an experienced frontend developer who enjoys building beautiful and efficient web applications. I'm a strong team player, committed to continuous learning and feedback-driven environments. My focus lies in creating visually appealing and high-performing web applications that align with project specifications

CANTACTS



Saniflex_1



Saniflex-1



+233(0)596038258



Accra Bortianor



owusuwilliam2344@gmail.com

INTERESTS

Passionate about innovative problemsolving and committed to delivering work of the highest quality and reliability.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF ENERGY & NATURAL RESOURCES 2020 - PRESENT

STUDY BSC COMPUTER SCIENCE

ST. MARTIN'S SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

2015 - 2018

STUDY GENERAL SCIENCE

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

BECOMING CREATION LTD UK (2020 - PRESENT)

• Building and implementing user interfaces and functionalities using HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT

UX/UI DESIGNER

BEECOMING CARE SERVICES UK (2023 - PRESENT)

- •Creates an information architecture of how the content and features of the product will be organized. Creates wireframes and prototypes to visualize the product's layout and functionality.
- FRONTEND DEVELOPER BOTECH DEVELOPMENTS (2021 - PRESENT)

PERSONAL SKILLS



CSS

JAVASCRIPT





